Adam Myers

253-973-4934 - adam@amyers.io

MISSION STATEMENT

I quit my job several years ago to backpack Europe alone and I embrace challenge and adventure. I was a non-traditional student who studied Music but fell in love with Computer Science and the possibilities that it affords the world. During my time away from school I learned how to engage and inspire those around me.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

December 2014

University of Puget Sound - Tacoma, Washington

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Python 2.7, Flask, Ruby 2.2.0, Rails 4.0, Java, Postgres SQL

Natural Language Processing: spaCy, Parsey McParseface, BeautifulSoup, Stanford NLP libraries

Machine Learning: tensorflow, Log linear models

Tools: Docker, Git, Asana, Code Climate CLI, Semaphore CI, ValentinaDB

Web Programming: HTML5/CSS3, SASS, CSS Frameworks, Basic JavaScript and jQuery

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Tyemill – Software Analyst www.tyemill.com

September 2015 – Present

- Helped build a Machine Learning Service to analyze various streams of data that empowered largescale economic theory and development.
- Created a suite to programmatically extract and parse data from financial documents by using natural language parsers for use in Machine Learning applications.

Tyemill – Full-Stack Software Developer Intern www.tyemill.com June 2015 - September 2015

- Developed features for Ruby on Rails applications that support a broad base of uses, ranging from investment analysis to economic development.
- Created the model and all backend algorithms to efficiently calculate correlation coefficients dynamically that was then displayed to user via frontend HighChart.

PROJECTS

Web Development – Business Website http://www.thecopperdoor.net

• Designed and built a website to exceed company's expectations using HTML, CSS, and Javascript only. Website is Responsive and uses the Untappd API to dynamically build the tap-list via jQuery.

Ruby on Rails – Subject Pool Management https://github.com/ammyers/SPM

September 2014 – May 2015

 Developed a Rails application that allowed the Psychology Department to electronically manage their pool of student research subjects and studies